A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Audiovisual materials FA752
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation Audio, 3
  - Dr. Davidson's Part II: Morning and Afternoon; RKD-EFD Meeting Part II, 1973 November 20; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15311)
    a.m., p.m
  - GHT Conference International River Basins, 1974 February 22; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15312)
  - MPT Conference and Bellagio Project on Higher Education for Development, 1974 February 11; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15313)
  - Rober Roosa - The International Monetary System: Past, Present, and Future, 1973 March 6; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15314)
  - JHK Wed Morn Meeting (Gilbert White - speaker), 1974 March 27; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15315)
  - Speaker: Dr. Marshall Shulman, 1974 April 24; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15317)
    Wednesday Morning Meeting (9:30-10:30-11:00)
  - Lester Brown - Overseas Development council, 1974 February 27; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15318)
  - Partisan Review Humanities Conference Transcribed Martin C?.., 1974 May 10; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15319)
  - Michael Novak "The Cure of Souls" ("Seven Theologians"), 1974 June 22; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15320)
  - JHK Staff Meeting: Prof. Joel Fleishmon "Role of Humanities in Public Policy Analysis", 1974 May 22; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15321)
    9:30-11:30
  - Sheldon Segal V-P for Bio Medical Sci. Div. of the population Council, 1974 June 5; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15322)
    Wednesday Morning Meeting
  - MPT Conference and Bellagio Project on Higher Education for Development, 1974 February 12; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15323)
  - Michael Novak Conference, 1974 May 29; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15324)
  - JHK Medical Conf - C? on Critical Choices, 1974 June 26; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15325)
  - Plant Symposium - ACB, 1974 June 10; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15326)
  - C. Fred Bergsten, "The Implications of Shortages and Inflation for the International System.", 1974 July 31; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15327)
  - Arts Program Recording Project Meeting, 1974 September 20; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15328)
  - Ambassador John R. Stevenson Attends United Nations Law of the Sea Conference in Venezuela, 1974 October 2; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15329)
  - Jon Rhode - Interview Art Recording Mtg - HK, 1974 October 1 and 11; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15330)
  - Antonio Carillo-Flores Secretary General World Population Conference on "All Things Considered", 1974 July 31; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15331)
  - Options; Report from Bucharest U.N. World Population Conference, 1974 September 29; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15332)
  - 2nd RF forum on Arts, 1974 November 18-19; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15333)
  - Derek Rok and JHK discuss Africa with Staff, 1975 March 13; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15334)
  - JC - Elizabeth Janewdy, 1975 March 26; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15335)
  - Dr. Virginia A Church, 1975 April 23; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15336)
  - James Hester - Past President of NYU - President of UN University, 1975 June 4; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15337)
  - Colin Turnbull, 1975 February 5; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 2, Reel AV 15338)
  - Bellagio Conference Insecticides, 1974; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15339)
  - Bellagio Conference Insecticides, 1974; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15340)
  - Eleanor Holmes Norton, 1976 February 11; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15341)
  - Humanities Centers, 1976 March 18; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15342)
  - Robert Coles, 1976 February 25; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15343)
  - Dr. Josue Gonzalez: Bilingual and Bicultural Education, 1976 May 19; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15344)
  - Wed Morning Meetings Chaired by Elmore Jackson, 1976 July 26; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15345)
  - George Bundy, 1976 July 14; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15346)
  - Dr. Percy ??.., 1976 July 21; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15347)
  - Margaret Mead - Women in Agriculture, 1974 December 18; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15348)
  - JC Meeting Richard Sennett Conference, 1975 January 31; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15349)
  - JC - Dissent Meeting, 1975 May 1; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15350)
  - Dr. Raymond Moody, 1975 December 8; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15351)
  - Jacques Barzun, 1976 December AV 15; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15352)
  - Maurice Langham, 1977 January 19; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15353)
  - Rostow, 1977 January 12; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15354)
  - Stuart Mott - Foundations and Politics, 1977 February 2; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15355)
  - Women's History - Joan Gadol, 1977 March 9; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15356)
  - Herbert Gutman, 1977 January 5; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15357)
  - HK Meeting Underground TV Meeting, 1975 May 22; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15358)
  - Ann Coste - Discussing Programs of Rockefeller Family Fund, 1977 May 19; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15359)
  - Sir Leon Radzinowicz Subject: The growth of crime; the international experience, 1977 April 4; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15360)
  - Paul Friedman, 1977 June 29; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15361)
  - Max Lerner New York Post "Third Century America", 1977 April 26; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15362)
  - Allard Lowenstein, 1977 October 31; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15363)
  - Ben Hooks - NAACP, 1977 November 16; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15364)
  - Dr. David Shear and Michael Feldstein Meeting on USAID Programs in the Sahel, 1977 November 23; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15365)
  - Frances Fitzgerald, 1976 November 18; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15366)
  - Livingston Biddle Re: Government and Grants for Arts and Humanities, 1977 March 23; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15367)
  - Edward T Hall, 1977 December 14; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15368)
  - Willrich talk on Energy program, 1977 April 28; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 3, Reel AV 15369)
  - Villa Conference - Management of Interdependence, 1975 May 11; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15370)
  - Villa Conference - Management of Interdependence, 1975 May 12; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15371)
  - Villa Conference - Management of Interdependence, 1975 May 13; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15372)
  - Days 1 and 2 Bellagio Conference, Humanities and Social Thought, 1977 June 2-3; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15373)
  - Untitled, Sound; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15374)
  - Untitled, Sound; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15375)
  - Duplicates June 6 Session, 1977 June 6; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15376)
  - Program and Policy Value Consensus Conference, 1978 March 28-29; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15377)
  - Bellagio Humanities Conference, 1974; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15378)
  - Bellagio Humanities Conference, 1974; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15379)
  - Bellagio Humanities Conference, 1974; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15380)
  - Bellagio Humanities Conference, 1974; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15381)
  - Conference on the Possibility of Cooperation between the NEH and the Private Humanities Foundations, 1980 July 17; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15382)
  - Conference on Relationship between Humanities and Public Policy, 1980 July 17; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15383)
  - SJS, 1979 February 21; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15384)
  - Women, Society and Work Conference The Journal of Family History and Signs, 1978 September 21-22; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15385)
  - Women, Society and Work Conference The Journal of Family History and Signs, 1978 September 22; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15386)
  - Judge Leon Higginbotham, 1978 June 21; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15387)
  - Semiotics Seminar - Professors Thomas Winner and Thomas Sebrok of the University of Indiana at the RF, 1978 October 4; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15388)
    10 a.m. Meeting
  - DBG Meeting - Alternate careers for Ph.D.s - II, 1974 October 11; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15389)
  - Program and Policy Underdeveloped Areas Center Studies, 1980 April 7; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15390)
  - Program and Policy Underdeveloped Areas Center Studies, 1980 April 7; Sound,; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 4, Reel AV 15391)